Von Tilzer / Gumm Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1921-1958 (Box 2-10)
  - H. Harold Gumm
    - Miscellaneous correspondence from the files of H. Harold Gumm (by subject):
      - Banks (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Domestic help (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Health care and interrment (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Hotels (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Investments (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Sympathy notices (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Address list [manuscript, in the hand of H. Harold Gumm] (Box-folder 10/9)
  - William V. Goldie
    - Broadway Music Corp. (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Mahoney, Jack (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Mitchell, Mae (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Phillips, Nizer, Benjamin & Krim (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Sherwood, Vince (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Correspondence from others to the following:
    - Dorner, Charles J. (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Preston, Walter (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Singer, Dolph (Box-folder 10/18)
- Music (Box 11-45)
  - Vocal Music, Manuscripts (Box 11-25)
    Contains lead sheets (with or without text), piano scores, piano-vocal scores and more. Mostly undated.
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Abba dabba [also known as Monkey song] Stone, Piano; text (Box-folder 11/1)
    - ABC Medley (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Abie and me and the baby Lew Brown, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; parts (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Abraham (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Absent minded Mary Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (without words); 1st violin; text (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Aching hearts (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Achoo song Chas Robinson (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Ah-ah-ah-ah I'll tell my Ma, Text (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Ain't that guy got nerve, Piano; text (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Ain't that mean (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Alabama bound (Box-folder 11/11)
    - All by our lonely, 1st violin part (conductor) (Box-folder 11/12)
    - All comes out in the wash Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 11/13)
    - All sorts of eyes (Box-folder 11/14)
    - All the girls lovely girls (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Alley (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Alone in the dark (duet from Mad Love), Piano; text (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Along the Milky Way, Piano; text (Box-folder 11/18)
    - America (Box-folder 11/19)
    - American bookmakers (Box-folder 11/20)
    - An angel (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Angel of love Tommy Ray (Box-folder 11/22)
    - Anton, he's a craze (Box-folder 11/23)
    - Any old man will do (duet, Eleanor & Pussy) (Box-folder 11/24)
    - Any old night is moonlight when you're on Broadway, Text (Box-folder 11/25)
    - Arrah go long with you see Green in your eye (Box-folder 11/26)
    - At the lovers' ball (Box-folder 11/27)
    - At the old town pump, Piano; six saxophones; text (Box-folder 11/28)
    - At the Yiddish wedding dance (Box-folder 11/29)
    - Attic Harry Von Tilzer, Phil White (Box-folder 11/30)
    - Auld lang syne Frank Fogarty, Piano (Box-folder 11/31)
    - Babette [Minuet], Piano (Box-folder 11/32)
    - Baby, Piano; female quartet; cornet part (Box-folder 11/33)
    - Baby o' mine (Box-folder 11/34)
    - Baby, save your kisses for me Frank Tinarey, Fred Strasser, Joe Hartig, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 11/35)
    - Baby smiles at me, Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/36)
    - Bad, bad baby, Kids' routine (Box-folder 11/37)
    - Baldy (Box-folder 11/38)
    - Bamboo bungalow (Box-folder 11/39)
    - Band played Dixie (Box-folder 11/40)
    - Barnyard gale (Box-folder 11/41)
    - Bass viol, Male quartet (Box-folder 11/42)
    - Bathing Ben Welch (Box-folder 11/43)
    - Batter up, Male quartet (Box-folder 11/44)
    - Battery F (Box-folder 11/45)
    - Battle for living Frank Fogarty, Grace Edmonds, Piano (Box-folder 11/46)
    - The beautiful snow Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 11/47)
    - Billy's Betty girl (Box-folder 11/48)
    - Bing bing, Text (Box-folder 11/49)
    - The bluebird's lament, Text (Box-folder 11/50)
    - Blues Pinkard, Marian Lewis, Lead sheet; trombone part (Box-folder 11/51)
    - Booby-house (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Book (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Book song, Columbia show. (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Bridget McCann, you're a jewel Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Bring back Rowland, Pall Mall 3, Quartet; male trio (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Broadway, Text (Box-folder 12/6)
    - The Broadway handicap (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Broadway must be heaven, Bassoon part (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Broadway scale of love, Piano; text (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Broadway touch, Text (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Broken heart Ed Barnes (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Brother Mike Frank Fogarty, Piano (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Brotherly love Jack Norworth, Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Brutus Caesar (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Bubbles Wells (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Busy bee Ben (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Buy a liberty bond for the baby Ed Moran, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Bye and bye, Quartets (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Cabby, Piano (Box-folder 12/19)
    - Can't get away from me Harry Hastings (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Can't keep my eyes Bergeron, King (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Can't you see Nat Vincent, Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/22)
    - Captain Curly Head (Box-folder 12/23)
    - Carolina sunshine Wm. K. Wells; Pall Mall 3; 6 Kirksmiths; Rover; Mrs. Thornton, Piano; trios; quartets (Box-folder 12/24)
    - Castle in Spain Sam Howe (Box-folder 12/25)
    - Cat is away (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Cause of it all Myrtle & Pauli (Box-folder 12/27)
    - Celia (1903) Harry Wellman, Text; contract (Box-folder 12/28)
    - Charity Bensee & Baird (Box-folder 12/29)
    - Cheat (Box-folder 12/30)
    - Cheer up Big City 4, Piano-vocal (without words); quartet (Box-folder 12/31)
    - Cherie (Box-folder 12/32)
    - Chicken farm (Box-folder 12/33)
    - Choo choo car (Box-folder 12/34)
    - Chop sticks Jack Norworth (Box-folder 12/35)
    - Christmas (Box-folder 12/36)
    - Christofo Colombo Al Piantadosi (Box-folder 12/37)
    - Circus (excerpts) Leo Hoyt (Box-folder 12/38)
    - The circus band (Box-folder 12/39)
    - Come and dance with me (Box-folder 12/40)
    - Come back to me (Spanish coon song) Frank Hayes (Box-folder 12/41)
    - Come on over Harry Von Tilzer, Grace Fisher, Lead sheet; text (Box-folder 12/42)
    - Come on Susan, come on Joe, Text (Box-folder 12/43)
    - Come to the circus (Box-folder 12/44)
    - Consequences Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 12/45)
    - Coochi coochi coo, Text (Box-folder 12/46)
    - Cotton blossom Sue (Box-folder 12/47)
    - Couldn't happen to me (Box-folder 12/48)
    - Country (Box-folder 12/49)
    - Croquet Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 12/50)
    - Cry baby (Box-folder 12/51)
    - Cuckoo reel (Box-folder 12/52)
    - The custard pie song (Act II, no. 12) (Box-folder 12/53)
    - Curiosity (Box-folder 12/54)
    - Cute little plane for two (Box-folder 12/55)
    - Daddy knows (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Dance medley Tom Overholt (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Dance of death (Finale, Act I) (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Dancing by the sea, Text (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Dat spoony rag W. Raymond Walker, Piano (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Days (new patter) Arranged by Ed. Smalle, Piano (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Dear old mother days (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Disappointed, Piano (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Discovered you, Vocal parts (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Dixie Romain & La Pearl; Leslie Connell Trio, Trio; male quartet (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Does anybody want my Fido? (1919) Garfield Kilgour, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Does you love Honey (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Doing hi bit (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Doll Mrs. Sydney, Male quartet (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Dolly shook her golden curls (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Do they do those things in New York Edward Clark, 1st violin part (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Do you get me? (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Done before, Piano (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Don't do that Ed Moran, Harry Von Tilzer, Lillian Lorraine, Piano-vocal; piano; parts; text (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Don't know where, Quartets (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Don't make me laugh (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Don't say good-bye Dannie O'Neil, Piano; lead sheet (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Don't stop, Text (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Don't talk about home Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Don't wake me up (Box-folder 13/25)
    - Don't you remember me?, Text (Box-folder 13/26)
    - Doo-da (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Doo dah dey (Box-folder 13/28)
    - Doodle doodle doo (Box-folder 13/29)
    - Dooley did the booly booly, Text (Box-folder 13/30)
    - Down by the river Nile George Totten Smith, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 13/31)
    - Down in Madagascar land (Box-folder 13/32)
    - Down in rag-time row (Box-folder 13/33)
    - Down on the farm (Box-folder 13/34)
    - Dreams Sterling 3, Piano; vocal quartet; trio (Box-folder 13/35)
    - Dreams come true (Box-folder 13/36)
    - Ebenezer (Box-folder 13/37)
    - Egypt (Box-folder 13/38)
    - Eli (Box-folder 13/39)
    - Ely, good bye (Box-folder 13/40)
    - End of world (Box-folder 13/41)
    - Every morning, Text (Box-folder 13/42)
    - Ev'ry tear is a smile (in an Irishman's heart), Piano (Box-folder 13/43)
    - Everybody knows that I love you, dear, Text (Box-folder 13/44)
    - Everybody's on the make (Box-folder 13/45)
    - Exposition four, Flute and trombone parts (Box-folder 13/46)
    - Eyes can't see me (Box-folder 13/47)
    - Faces across the bar Harry Von Tilzer, Fred Nolan (Box-folder 13/48)
    - Fairy tales (Box-folder 13/49)
    - The famous galloping girl (Box-folder 13/50)
    - Far away look Harry Von Tilzer, Parts (Box-folder 13/51)
    - Far far away (Box-folder 13/52)
    - Farewell Miss Clarabelle (Box-folder 13/53)
    - Farmer, Piano (Box-folder 13/54)
    - Father said something to mother (Box-folder 13/55)
    - Finger in the pie (Box-folder 13/56)
    - Fool out of Broadway (Box-folder 13/57)
    - French Phil White (Box-folder 13/58)
    - Funny little walk (Box-folder 13/59)
    - Game of love Childs in F, Piano (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Ganges River (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Garden of lies (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Gay Paree Midgie Miller (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Gee ain't I glad I'm home (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Genevieve (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Gentleman Charlotte Parry (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Georgia Sterling Trio, Quartet arrangement (Box-folder 14/8)
    - German heaven (Box-folder 14/9)
    - The ghost of the ukelele, Piano; text (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Ginger (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Girl for me Millard & Gay Lorette (Box-folder 14/12)
    - The girl I left (Box-folder 14/13)
    - The girl I left before I left (1909) Mahoney, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Girl song, Three parts (Box-folder 14/15)
    - A girl who don't like the boys (Box-folder 14/16)
    - A girl who's one of the boys (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Give me the right to call you mine Harry Von Tilzer; Sterling Trio, Guitar/vocal; vocal trio (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Give my love to Nellie (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Golden days, Piano; lead sheet (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Goodbye Antonio (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Goodbye Susan, goodbye Jane (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Good for nothing Doris Wilson, Three vocal parts (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Good man now (Box-folder 14/24)
    - The good ole song of the blue and gray (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Good ship Honeymoon (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Good time Charlie, Text (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Gorilla grab (Box-folder 14/28)
    - Got nothing (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Gowns Herlein, Piano; text (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Grape juice bill (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Great big world (Box-folder 14/32)
    - Green in your [me] eye (also known as Arrah go long with you) Eddie Moran, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; instrumental parts; text (Box-folder 14/33)
    - The greeter May Hickey (Box-folder 14/34)
    - Gumshoe man (Box-folder 14/35)
    - Gunga, Special - Big City 4. (Box-folder 14/36)
    - Hackensack (Box-folder 14/37)
    - Hannah's going to get me sure (Box-folder 14/38)
    - Happy hunting ground (Box-folder 14/39)
    - Harry (Box-folder 14/40)
    - Harvest days, Piano (Box-folder 14/41)
    - Harvest moon Elm City 4, Male quartet; female quartet (Box-folder 14/42)
    - Has anybody got an umbrella (Box-folder 14/43)
    - Have a heart Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 14/44)
    - Have you forgotten so soon? (1935) Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (with guitar); piano (Box-folder 14/45)
    - Have you no heart (Box-folder 14/46)
    - He learned about women from me, Text (Box-folder 14/47)
    - He was a hero in the army Phil Baker (Box-folder 14/48)
    - He was talking (Box-folder 14/49)
    - He's always doing something, Piano (Box-folder 14/50)
    - Hebrew sailor song Sam Howe (Box-folder 14/51)
    - Hello! Boys, I'm back again Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; parts (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Help, Piano; lead sheet (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Hennessey (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Here's your hat (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Highland Mary (Dance for) Eddie Foy (Box-folder 15/5)
    - The hippodrome evangelist, Piano (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Hm hm let's see Billy Montgomery, George Perry, Piano; parts (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Hokum (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Holding hands (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Homesick (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Honestly think (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Honey bee (1926) Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Honeymoon R. C. McPherson, Chris Smith, Text (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Honoloo, Text (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Honolula cabaret, Piano (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Hot time (Box-folder 15/16)
    - How about tonight? (Box-folder 15/17)
    - How can I help (Box-folder 15/18)
    - How much am I bid Addison Burkhardt, Text (Box-folder 15/19)
    - How would you like in my auto car (Box-folder 15/20)
    - Huckle (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Husband Miss Le Roy, Piano (Box-folder 15/22)
    - I can't guess that you love me, Text (Box-folder 15/23)
    - I could be coaxed Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (partial); text (Box-folder 15/24)
    - I don't count for nothin', Text (Box-folder 15/25)
    - I don't want another girlie (Box-folder 15/26)
    - I feel it (Box-folder 15/27)
    - I gave her that Ed Moran, Dave Weisburg, Dave Kaplan, Piano; text (Box-folder 15/28)
    - I got an idea Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 15/29)
    - I hate you (Box-folder 15/30)
    - I heard different Adair and Gaylor, Piano (Box-folder 15/31)
    - I just came from old Missouri (Box-folder 15/32)
    - I know all about it now George Duval, Jr., Text (Box-folder 15/33)
    - I know just where she hangs out (Box-folder 15/34)
    - I know nothing of love Anna Ford, Piano; parts (Box-folder 15/35)
    - I left my old Kentucky home for you, Text (Box-folder 15/36)
    - I love a little lovin (Box-folder 15/37)
    - I love to make up with you (Box-folder 15/38)
    - I love you even more dan dat (Box-folder 15/39)
    - I might be coaxed but not by you Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 15/40)
    - I never knew that I loved you, Lead sheet (Box-folder 15/41)
    - I never that a girl like you, Piano (Box-folder 15/42)
    - I.O.U. (Box-folder 15/43)
    - I really hate to talk about myself, Text (Box-folder 15/44)
    - I sez Wimperis and Davidson/Davidson, Piano-vocal (without words); text (Box-folder 15/45)
    - I tried to make a fool out of B'way Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 15/46)
    - I used to be a regular actor (Box-folder 15/47)
    - I used to call her honey (Box-folder 15/48)
    - I want a boy Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; text (Box-folder 15/49)
    - I want a mama (Box-folder 15/50)
    - I want a man Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; text (Box-folder 15/51)
    - I want a playmate (Box-folder 15/52)
    - I want someone to float me Edward Clark, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 15/53)
    - I want to be good Frank Fay, Dave Dreyer, Piano-vocal; piano (Box-folder 15/54)
    - I want to be loved Margaret Ford, Al Doyle (Box-folder 15/55)
    - I want to be somebody's baby Ed Smalle, Jesse Greer, Lead with words (duet) (Box-folder 15/56)
    - I want you, Text (Box-folder 15/57)
    - I wish I were you (1911) Ballard Macdonald, Harry Piani, Lead sheet (Box-folder 15/58)
    - I won the family over (Box-folder 15/59)
    - I wouldn't be surprised, Piano (Box-folder 15/61)
    - I'd do as much for you, Text (Box-folder 16/1)
    - I'd do the same for you (Box-folder 16/2)
    - I'd like to change places with you, Text (Box-folder 16/3)
    - I'd like to meet the fella that wrote... (Box-folder 16/4)
    - If all the nurses were like you... Pauli, Piano (Box-folder 16/5)
    - If I catch the guy (Box-folder 16/6)
    - If I wait till the end of the world Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 16/7)
    - If it wasn't for you (Box-folder 16/8)
    - If old Bill Jones were here (Box-folder 16/9)
    - If the dreams that I dream come true Billy K. Wells, Piano (Box-folder 16/10)
    - If you don't think you ought to do Sterling & Moran, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 16/11)
    - If you don't want to lose you're chicken (Box-folder 16/12)
    - If you only had my disposition (1915) Albert Von Tilzer; arranged by Mornay D. Halm, Parts (Box-folder 16/13)
    - If you were mine, Text (Box-folder 16/14)
    - I'll be the boy you be the girl (Box-folder 16/15)
    - I'll be the words you'll be the music "Ruth" (Box-folder 16/16)
    - I'll be your Carmen if you be my toreador (Box-folder 16/17)
    - I'll be yours 'till Niagara Falls Harry R. Aurachev (Box-folder 16/18)
    - I'll get even with you (Box-folder 16/19)
    - I'll never pick a rose again, Text (Box-folder 16/20)
    - I'll tell my big brother on you (Box-folder 16/21)
    - Ill wind, Piano; text (Box-folder 16/22)
    - I'm a devil of a fellow don't you know (Box-folder 16/23)
    - I'm a little bit afraid of you, B'way, Piano; parts (Box-folder 16/24)
    - I'm an old sea dog, Text (Box-folder 16/25)
    - I'm ashamed to tell the rest Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 16/26)
    - I'm going down to beat my wife William F. Kirk, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 16/27)
    - I'm homesick Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (without words); text (Box-folder 16/28)
    - I'm so good to the manager (Box-folder 16/29)
    - I'm worried (Box-folder 16/30)
    - In a chimney corner Royal Musical Five, Violin part (Box-folder 16/31)
    - In an aeroplane built for two, Piano; text (Box-folder 16/32)
    - In childhood days Dick Knowles (Box-folder 16/33)
    - In de evenin' (1910) Alex Rogers, Will Marion Cook, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 16/34)
    - In dreamy Spain Alberto Rizzo, Piano (Box-folder 16/35)
    - In Ladyland (Box-folder 16/36)
    - In London town Sam Howe (Box-folder 16/37)
    - In Matteawan, Piano (Box-folder 16/38)
    - In Paree (Box-folder 16/39)
    - In the cottage on Poverty Street Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 16/40)
    - In the foolish-house (Box-folder 16/41)
    - In the good old Irish way, Piano; text (Box-folder 16/42)
    - In the land of the rising sun Samuel A. Massell, Piano (Box-folder 16/43)
    - In the springtime (Box-folder 16/44)
    - In you all my dreams come true, Text (Box-folder 16/45)
    - Indian love (Box-folder 16/46)
    - Indian summer moon Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 16/47)
    - Indian summer moon George A. Kershaw, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (3 copies); text (Box-folder 16/48)
    - Intermezzo Al Johns (Box-folder 16/49)
    - Ireland (Box-folder 16/50)
    - Irish home sweet home Me, Him & I, Piano; parts (Box-folder 16/51)
    - The Irish Jew-bi-lee, Text (Box-folder 16/52)
    - Irish melody (Box-folder 16/53)
    - Irish song Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 16/54)
    - Irish songs of yesterday, Piano (Box-folder 16/55)
    - Isn't my fault (Box-folder 16/56)
    - It ain't so awful Mabel (Box-folder 16/57)
    - It's a secret Ballard MacDonald, Billy Kilgard, Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/58)
    - It's my birthday everyday Eva Tanguay, Piano (Box-folder 16/59)
    - It's 100 to 1 he's in love (Box-folder 16/60)
    - I've got it on them all Eddie Foy, Text (Box-folder 16/61)
    - I've wasted my love on you Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; text (Box-folder 16/62)
    - Ivy twines (Box-folder 16/63)
    - Jack Smith rag Smalle, Piano (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Jakali (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Japanese moon Sam Howe (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Jean Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Jess (Special) De Noyer (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Jim Nosse, Vocal quartet (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Jingaboo (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Jingle bells 4 Virginia Girls, Piano (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Jingle jungle town (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Joe (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Just, Piano (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Just a little bit (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Just a little party (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Just an old jay Big City 4 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Just another poor man, Piano (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Just as if I didn't know White Sisters; Honey Hurst, Piano; parts; text (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Just as lonesome as you [also known as Let's play house] (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Just as Mother's was (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Just as we used to be Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Just because he's good to me Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Just like your dear old mother Harry Von Tilzer, Kaplan, Piano (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Just lonesome for you Arranged by Ed. Smalle, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 17/22)
    - Just nigger Parry (Box-folder 17/23)
    - Just one more (Box-folder 17/24)
    - June's brides, Piano (Box-folder 17/25)
    - K. W. (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Kalamazoo Prown & Jackson, Piano (Box-folder 17/27)
    - Katie Wood, Piano; text (Box-folder 17/28)
    - Keep away from Elaine, Text (Box-folder 17/29)
    - Keep Irish out Hanlon & Conrad (Box-folder 17/30)
    - Keep it in the family (Box-folder 17/31)
    - Kentucky Sue (Box-folder 17/32)
    - Kicking around (Box-folder 17/33)
    - Kiddie Koo (Box-folder 17/34)
    - King Solomon, Text (Box-folder 17/35)
    - Kisses for sale, Text (Box-folder 17/36)
    - Kissing rag Manning & Moore (Box-folder 17/37)
    - Kitty Rooney Arthur E. Behim, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 17/38)
    - Knit knit knit (Box-folder 17/39)
    - Knock a little louder Ephraham Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 17/40)
    - Lady Lou Sherwood Trio, Piano (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Lamp us on the campus Hi, Icho, Icho, 2nd violin part (Box-folder 18/2)
    - The land o' love Will Heelan, Herbert Walters, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Land of Eskimo, Columbia summer show. (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Language of the eyes (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Lantern dance, 1st violin part (Box-folder 18/6)
    - The lassie I know (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Last day Burr & Meyer (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Laughing song, Piano (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Laura Lee, Piano; text (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Leave it to Eva (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Lemon tree (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Leo Friedman (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Let me dream, dream, dream [also known as Mr. Dreamer], Text (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Let me see old Ireland, Piano (Box-folder 18/15)
    - Let's get acquainted (Box-folder 18/16)
    - Life ain't worth living George B. Alexander, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 18/17)
    - Life is one thing after another (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Life saver Larry Comer, Piano (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Life's what you make it Gus Van, Joe Scheuck, Piano (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Lights go out, Piano (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Like Kelly did (Box-folder 18/22)
    - Like telling a kid there ain't no Santa Claus, Text (Box-folder 18/23)